## **BRB Hospitals Ltd.**

77/A, East Rajabazar, West Panthapath, <u>Dhaka-1215</u>.

BHL - 05/372

# Date: 17/03/2020

# Office Circular

This is for the information of all concern that **Dr. Aurobindo Roy** has joined us as **Consultant** – **Radiology & Imaging** on Part Time Contractual basic on March 10, 2020. He will works 03(three) days in a week from 04.00 pm to 09.00 pm, whose personal profile is given hereunder:

#### **Personal Profile**

Dr. Aurobindo Roy
Consultant – Radiology & Imaging (BRB Hospitals Ltd.)
MBBS, MD (Radiology & Imaging), FCPS (Radiology)
Contact no – 01734323937



### 1. Education Qualification:

- MBBS Dhaka Medical College in 1999.
- MD (Radiology) BSMMU in 2010.
- FCPS (Radiology) BCPS in 2010.

# 2. Working Experience:

- Dr. Aurobindo Roy started his career as Resident Medical Officer, Radiology & Imaging at BSMMU from July, 2002.
- He worked as Medical Officer at District Hospital from December 2003 to August, 2005.
- He worked as Medical Officer, Radiology at Rangpur Medical College Hospital from August, 2005 to February, 2007.
- He worked as Resident Medical Officer, Radiology at BSSMU from February, 2007 to February 2010
- He worked as Consultant, Radiology at 300 bed hospital, Narayangonj from February, 2010 to May, 2012.
- He worked as Radiologist at Sir Salimullah Medical College from May, 2012 to June 2013.
- He has been working as Assistant Professor, Radiology at Dhaka Medical College from July, 2013.
- He has several publications on different topics published in different national Journals.

All concern are requested to extend their full cooperation in discharging his duties and responsibilities effectively.

For BRB Hospitals Ltd.

(S. M. Mofleuddin Ahmed)
Director HR & Administration

#### Distribution:

- 1. All Consultants.
- 2. All Department Head.

#### Information:

- 1. Hon'ble Chairman, for kind information.
- 2. Hon'ble Managing Director, for kind information
- 3. Chief Executive Officer
- 4. Director, Medical Services.
- 5. Dy. Director, Medical Services.
- 6. Office Copy/Master File.